(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
弄られて
Manipulated,
垂れ流す
and discharged,
音のない音
a soundless sound.
遍く
Spread far and wide,
名前を捨てたのね
you abandoned your name.
あなたのモザイクが泣いてる
Your mosaic is crying.
can not, can not, not, not, not deny
紛れもなく真実
it is undoubtedly the truth.
さあ 預けて
Come, entrust it to me,
回帰するように
as if returning.
エネルギーはサイクル そう いまは
The energy is a cycle, yes, right now.
無重力
Weightlessness,
象徴的なパレード
a symbolic parade.
この月夜に
On this moonlit night,
仰げよ仰げ
look up, look up.
completeness
鳴呼 命の灯を掲げ
Ah, hold up the light of life.
KiLLKiSS today 欺いて
KiLLKiSS today, deceive me.
KiLLKiSS today 抱きしめて
KiLLKiSS today, hold me tight.
ねえ 無防備だね
Hey, you're so defenseless.
美しい戯れに
In this beautiful play,
人は壊れてゆく
people fall apart.
鳴呼 狂おしく
Ah, so maddeningly.
'cuz we're all alone
'Cause we're all alone.
噛み締めてもまだ痛むなら
If it still hurts even when I bite down,
手を挙げ 希え
raise your hands and hope.
oh, when you bleed, 惑星にそう その影を伸ばせ
Oh, when you bleed, stretch that shadow along the planet.
ねえ 私の世界が知りたがっているわさ
Hey, my world wants to know.
you bleed, yes, bleed その血で 天の五線譜を書き換えれば
You bleed, yes, bleed; if you rewrite the staff of heaven with that blood...
KiLLKiSS today 欺いて
KiLLKiSS today, deceive me.
KiLLKiSS today 抱きしめて
KiLLKiSS today, hold me tight.
ねえ あからさまね
Hey, it's so obvious,
醜い終局に
at this ugly end.
すべてが変わってゆく
Everything is changing.
儚いのね
It's so fleeting.
そう このまま
Just like this,
壊れて
break apart.
BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY 細胞 LEVEL
Break away, break away, at a cellular level.
I DON'T NEED 不本意 現状 触れてる 姿 仕草
I don't need this unwilling current state, your touching and gestures,
滑稽でしょ DON'T YOU THINK?
it's comical, don't you think?
I'M SO LAZY 多分そう FINE SOUND 並べてるだけの人
I'm so lazy, maybe so; someone just lining up fine sounds,
TRASH TRASH TOSS AWAY DON'T YOU THINK?
IN THIS WORLD この頭には
In this world, in this head,
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL 舞い散る花びら
what beautiful dancing flower petals.
PARALLEL LIKE 飲みたいな
Parallel like, I want to drink it in.
誰もが 大体 C R A Z Y One
Everyone is mostly crazy, one.
一瞬の感情に RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
On a momentary emotion, ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on.
心は 95 狂気の サムライ
The heart is 95, a samurai of madness.
血走らせた目で 引くくらい
With bloodshot eyes, enough to make you recoil,
READY TO DIE
陽は昇り RISING あなたの空 SORA
The sun rises, rising, your sky, sora.
真っ黒な空 荒々しく 引きちぎって
A pitch-black sky, violently tearing it apart.
ほら その場所で 聞こえてくる
Look, from that place, you can hear it,
鼓動の仕掛け 轟くのは
the heartbeat's mechanism; what's roaring is
誰のじゃない 己の調べ
not someone else's, but one's own melody.
目の前に広がる
Spreading before my eyes...
世界はブルー
...the world is blue.
ひとまず さあ MOVE MOVE
For now, come on, MOVE MOVE.
Speak about 生き方
Speak about our way of life.
There's no need 何をそんなに
There's no need, why are you so...
張り切って偉そうに
...enthusiastic and acting so high and mighty?
Give me more, 愛をもっと
Give me more, more love.
右も左も
Both right and left,
知りもしないで笑いだ
Laughing without even knowing.
Don't you think? Don't you think?
ニヤリ影が笑う
A grinning shadow laughs.
世界は大概
The world is mostly...
CRAZY
折り返すように
Like turning back...
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
わかってもいない
You don't even understand
アレコレ
this and that.
Tell me something for the new era
偉大な期待の時代のバイブル
The bible of a great and hopeful era.
CLAP BACK
LOSIN' MY MIND
SHOOTING MY SIDE
SAVE IT あなたの その瞬間
SAVE IT, that moment of yours.
Maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong.
La-dee-la-lee-la-la la-lee-la
誰もが大概
Everyone is mostly...
CRAZY
一瞬の感情に
To the emotions of a moment,
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
心は 95%
My heart is 95%...
狂気のサムライ
a crazy samurai.
血走らせた目で
With bloodshot eyes,
Feel alive, ready to die.
ほら 陽は昇り
Look, the sun rises.
あなたの空 真っ黒な空
Your sky, a pitch black sky.
あらあら しくしく
Tearing and sobbing,
引きちぎって
tear it all away.
ほら その場所で
Look, in that place...
聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
I hear the mechanism of a heartbeat.
驚くのは まだこれから
The surprise is yet to come.
まだこれから
It's yet to come.
ああ 待ちわびて
Ah, tired of waiting.
時計の針 0時の街
The clock hands, the town at midnight.
猛々しく Raise your voice
Raise your voice ferociously.
ほら すぐそこで
Look, right there...
始まりだす孤高の宴
the solitary banquet begins.
奏でるのは 己の調べ
Playing my own melody.
唯一無二の 己の調べ
My one and only melody.
わーい！
Waaai!
Perhatian sang putri merak yang tertiup angin,
Attention, the wind-blown peacock princess,
aku Pavolia Reine dari hololive ID.
I'm Pavolia Reine from hololive ID.
Attention please, I'm Reine from hololive ID Gen 2.
皆様ごきげんよう、わたくしホロライブインドネシア二期生、パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの。
Good day everyone, I am Pavolia Reine from hololive Indonesia 2nd Gen.
And welcome to Pavolia Reine's "Peafowl of the Blue Flame"!
Yay! Pavolia Reine's 2025 Birthday! Welcome!
イェーイ、ようこそー！
Yay, welcome!
えっと、左上にハッシュタグがありまして...
Um, there's a hashtag on the upper left corner...
There's a hashtag on the upper left corner.
It reads #ReineMEPtember2025.
Which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past few years, yeah?
And if you guys have any thoughts throughout the live, anything...
...you can write it and I'll be looking forward to them.
ご感想、and everything, you guys can write...
Your thoughts, and everything, you guys can write...
Campur-campur deh ngomongnya waduh ya gitu deh pokoknya.
I'm mixing languages, oh well, it's just like that.
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live. You don't have to write it now.
今じゃなくても大丈夫です。
It's okay even if it's not right now.
But I will be waiting! Yes!
So just put any of your thoughts in the hashtag, okay?
And next, I want to talk about the concept of the stage.
Look at this! It's so cool, right?
There's mysterious flame, mysterious locks...
...mysterious cans, mysterious... where's the liquid?
Well there was like a blue liquid there, but I mean you saw it, right? Yeah.
If you, um, I guess if you think of fire or flame, you know...
Usually you guys think of the color red, right? Automatically.
そうですね、火と言えばですね、赤のイメージが強いかもしれませんが...
Right, when you think of fire, the image of red might be strong...
But actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Iya nggasih?
But actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Right?
But actually, 実はですね、青い炎が一番強いと思います。
But actually, I think the blue flame is the strongest.
Yeah. So that's the theme of today's birthday.
I want to show you guys just how hot a blue flame can be
through hot songs...
...and songs that will make you feel, adu gerah banget, so atsui, so woo! Gitu deh pokoknya.
...and songs that will make you feel, oh it's so hot, so hot, so woo! Like that.
Just look forward to it, okay?
And the songs we've sang today... we have two songs.
The first one was "Kill Kiss".
そうですね、すごく好きな曲で、Avec Musique様の「Kill Kiss」です。
Right, it's a song I really like, "Kill Kiss" by Avec Musique.
そして2曲目は、私がすごい大好きな...
And the second song was from a unit I really love...
...プロセカのユニット、Vivid BAD SQUAD様の「CRAZY」でした。
...the Proseka unit Vivid BAD SQUAD, it was "CRAZY".
And the second song was "CRAZY" from a unit...
...I really really like from Proseka, by Vivid BAD SQUAD.
I hope you guys enjoyed it! Yay!
Emang kayak Reine tuh suka banget gitu sama lagunya.
Reine really likes the song.
Jadi masih akan ada lebih banyak lagi.
So there's still going to be more.
There's gonna be way more more more more songs...
...and I'm sure there's a lot of guests.
I hope you guys are excited for them!
これからもね、もっともっと熱くなるからね、ゲストも、many many many many...
From now on, it's going to get hotter and hotter, and there'll be many many guests...
But for now, I'm gonna sing
one of my original songs.
Do you guys know what it is?
The next song is... Love Me Love Me.
ずっと君の隣
Always by your side...
じっと見てるばかり
...just staring at you.
愛 愛 止まない雨
Love, love, the unending rain.
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in the world.
A, K, B, 刻むように
A, K, B, like carving it in.
そ、今この手に
There, now in my hands...
泣いた痛みさえも愛のカタチ
...even the pain of crying is a form of love.
運命に結ばれた小指は握る約束をしよう
Let's make a promise to hold our fate-bound pinkies.
LOVE ME LOVE ME
私がいらない
I don't need myself...
LOVE ME LOVE ME
君がいらない
I don't need you...
ギュッと抱きしめたら
If I hold you tight...
きっと逃げられない
...you surely won't escape.
チクタク針が回る
Tick-tock, the hands turn.
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in the world.
K, E, S, 交わすように
K, E, S, like an exchange.
カ、ジョ、オシ殺して
Crushing the emotions...
泣いた悲鳴さえも愛のメロディ
...even the crying screams are a melody of love.
運命に結ばれた小指は握る約束をしよう
Let's make a promise to hold our fate-bound pinkies.
LOVE ME LOVE ME
私がいらない
I don't need myself...
LOVE ME LOVE ME
君がいらない
I don't need you...
愛して
Love me...
愛され
...be loved.
離れられない
We can't be separated.
You and me
二人きりで
Just the two of us.
Give me your love
願うほど
The more I wish...
したたる赤色
...the more the red color drips.
何もかも全て縛る愛を
A love that binds everything...
もっと 頂戴
...give me more.
私がいらない
I don't need myself...
LOVE ME LOVE ME
君がいらない
I don't need you...
LOVE ME LOVE ME
ま、こんなもんでいいか
Well, this much is fine.
あ、そろそろ闇にしようや
Ah, it's about time to make it dark.
手抜き 手に入れ無理
Corner-cutting, I got the impossible.
それを大事にするなご愁傷様売り
Don't cherish that, my condolences for the sale.
いつか来る 後悔消せるかは今の自分次第
Whether I can erase the coming regret depends on my current self.
やるだけやったね 誰かじゃなくて未来の自分に嫌われないように
I did my best, so my future self won't hate me.
痺れてしまうのだっけ
I wonder if I'm going numb.
目の前の壁だったっけ
Was it the wall in front of me?
勝手に理想それで結構
Self-indulgent ideals? That's fine.
あとはひたすら前に進むだけ Yeah
Now, I just keep moving forward, yeah.
逆らえれば耐えるほどに
The more I resist and endure...
研ぎ澄まされていく時が 爽快だろう
...the time I become sharpened is exhilarating, right?
待て いけるはず
Wait, I should be able to go.
まだ やれるはず
I can still do it.
ヤバババナ ぶちかます番だ
Yabababana, it's time to let it rip.
さあ歌え踊れ騒げ 突き抜けてんのかアハ
Now sing, dance, make some noise! Are you breaking through? Aha!
ヤバババナ ガッと飛ばす場外
Yabababana, blasting it out of the park!
覚悟で決めた限界なんて 速攻超えちゃって超速攻
Overcome those limits set by resolve instantly, super instantly!
大体 そんな感じ
Generally, it's something like that.
サンサン 異常のアンサー
Sun-sun, an abnormal answer.
強豪の計画 利益上昇
The plan of the strong, profits rising.
踊るがままに
Just keep on dancing.
ヤバババナ ぶちかます番だ
Yabababana, it's time to let it rip.
さあ歌え踊れ騒げ 盛り上がれ バラバラバラ
Now sing, dance, make some noise! Get excited, bara-bara-bara!
邪念なら まだまだメラメラ
If it's wicked thoughts, they're still burning bright
ガンガンで 振るいな 運命(ごめ)に
Rock it hard, shake it off, for your fate
Just 1 point 徐々に
Just 1 point, gradually
何があったって 俺は俺
No matter what happens, I am me
どんどん進んでる 後悔ねぇ
Moving forward and forward, no regrets
逃げ出したいくらいが 本番
When you want to run away, it's the real show
デビュー 手の平返しは ロマン
The debut, the sudden turn of events, is a romance
重ねる努力から
From the accumulation of effort...
打ち下ろす K.O!
Striking down, K.O!
ヤパパパナブ カモスバンダ
Yap-papa-ba-na-bu kamosu vanda
さあ歌え踊れ騒げ すかびびってんのさ ハハ！
Now sing, dance, make some noise! Are you scared? Haha!
ヤパパパナブ カモスバンダ
Yap-papa-ba-na-bu kamosu vanda
かっ飛ばせ場外！
Hit it out of the park!
頭で決めて 限界なんて
Deciding with your head, about limits...
当然いってんじゃ ちょっと BAN!
It's only natural, a bit of a BAN!
気になる その感じ
I'm curious about that feeling
良い笑顔の味
The taste of a good smile
同時見学に 急行中
Rushing to a simultaneous observation
驚くのなるほうへ
Towards the place that becomes surprising
ヤパパパナブ カモスバンダ
Yap-papa-ba-na-bu kamosu vanda
さあ歌え踊れ騒げ 揚げ足取られたって
Now sing, dance, make noise! Even if they find fault...
邪念なら まだまだメラメラ
If it's wicked thoughts, they're still burning bright
ヤパパパナブ カモスバンダ
Yap-papa-ba-na-bu kamosu vanda
段違いのハイに
To a different level of high
燃え尽きて灰に
Burning out into ashes
なってるでも最後
It's becoming, but in the end
ラッキー 開眼！
Lucky eye-opening!
ヤパパパナブ カモスバンダ
Yap-papa-ba-na-bu kamosu vanda
かっ飛ばせ場外！
Hit it out of the park!
お先に失礼 サラバ
Excuse me for going ahead, farewell
ヤパパパスの果て
To the end of Yapapa-su
気になる その感じ
I'm curious about that feeling
良い笑顔の味
The taste of a good smile
同時見学に 急行中
Rushing to a simultaneous observation
驚くのなるほうへ
Towards the place that becomes surprising
ヤパパパナブ カモスバンダ
Yap-papa-ba-na-bu kamosu vanda
さあ歌え踊れ騒げ 揚げ足取られたって
Now sing, dance, make noise! Even if they find fault...
邪念なら まだまだメラメラ
If it's wicked thoughts, they're still burning bright
夜の始まりさ バニーガール 誘惑される
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl, being seduced
言に弾け飛ぶ 本当に 愛を乾杯
Bursting with words, truly a toast to love
伝えられなくても
Even if it can't be conveyed
恋の始まりさ バニーガール 誰かも
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl, whoever it is
穿って澄んだ 君の眼を 孕んで
Piercing and clear, bearing your eyes
さあ 刻なステップ 刻んで
Now, carve those elegant steps
仕事帰りの 疲れは
The fatigue from returning from work
私とこのグラスに
Pour it into this glass with me
そう 自分好みに 縋って
Yes, clinging to your own preference
世間に対する気持ち
The feelings towards the world
私に注いでみない?
Won't you try pouring them into me?
ありきたりな ラブソングでも
Even with an ordinary love song
愛が零れているの
Love is overflowing
それでも汚れるのんで 君を見ればわかるの
Even so, by getting dirty, I'll know by looking at you
下を向く 君の眼を
Looking down at your eyes
無理やり事はしない
I won't force anything
だから そんな顔せず 手を差し伸べて ほら
So don't make that face, reach out your hand, look
夜の始まりさ バニーガール 誘惑される
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl, being seduced
言に弾け飛ぶ 本当に 愛を乾杯
Bursting with words, truly a toast to love
伝えられなくても
Even if it can't be conveyed
恋の始まりさ バニーガール 誰かも
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl, whoever it is
穿って澄んだ 君の眼を 孕んで
Piercing and clear, bearing your eyes
君の愛を知った気で
Thinking I knew your love
灰になっていて
Becoming ashes
感度去っていて
Losing sensitivity
毎日泣いていてさ
Crying every day
それくらいがいいんでしょう?
That much is just right, isn't it?
さあ 刻なステップ 刻んで
Now, carve those elegant steps
君の顔色にまでは
Even to the point of your complexion
真っ白になってきているから
Because it's becoming pure white
私をあげるわ バニーガール 誘惑される
I'll give you myself, Bunny Girl, being seduced
言に弾け飛ぶ 本当に 愛を乾杯
Bursting with words, truly a toast to love
伝えられてるはず
It should have been conveyed
夜の始まりさ バニーガール 誰かも
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl, whoever it is
穿って澄んだ 君の眼を 孕んで
Piercing and clear, bearing your eyes
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ヤベェヤムレヤメ ヤマワラエ
Yabe yamu re yame yama warae
アホ心酔しちゃって 徘徊曖昧シャットダウン
Dazed and infatuated, wandering in a vague shutdown
警鐘のランウェイ 逃げ切れワンダー
The runway of warning bells, run through the wonder
急逝ステーションはダイブ ムービング選択肢
Sudden death station is a dive, moving options
引き金ダーリン さあ パッパパパ モンスターマインド
Pull the trigger, darling, now p-p-p-p monster mind
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
諸道幻覚乱入エスカレート 煙に巻かすボス目覚める
Hallucinations intrude and escalate, the boss awakens
紳士淑女 ダーティーピープル ヤミヤミ ジャスティス
Ladies and gentlemen, dirty people, Yami Yami Justice
ワンチャン狙うジャックポット 寝癖はガード
無理矢理仕掛けるなるべく爆笑
Jackpot aiming for a chance, guard the bedhead
Force the setup, making them roar with laughter
完成 完成 完成 お裾分け
Completion, completion, completion, sharing the spoils
アズキズキ パラッパ 冷めないうちに
Heart-throbbing, p-r-p, before it cools down
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
アズキズキ パラッパ お味はいかが？
Heart-throbbing, p-r-p, how's the taste?
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ア、足りない まだ足りないわ
Ah, it's not enough, it's still not enough
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ア、脳裏に まだ足りないわ
Ah, in my mind, it's still not enough
右に 右に
To the right, to the right,
最高にハイで更新中
Updating at the absolute high
シ、虚構のバリア 駆け足でロップ
Sh- barrier of fiction, running with a lop
右か左か
Is it right or left?
逃げるが勝ちだ
Running away is a victory
ド、土星のドクター 空気のダンスホール
D- doctor of Saturn, an atmospheric dance hall
卵にウサギだ バランスは整った
Rabbit in the egg, the balance is set
サ、ベイビーベイビーベイビー もじかふがないわ
Sa- baby baby baby, there's no alphabet
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ラ、リルラレリル 竦めている裏
Ra- rirurayeriru, shrinking behind it
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ハ、ドキドキ ファイヤー ルージュを点けて
Ha- heart-throbbing fire, put on some rouge
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ハ、ドキドキ ファイヤー 深紅のリズム
Ha- heart-throbbing fire, crimson rhythm
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ア、足りない まだ足りないわ
Ah, it's not enough, it's still not enough
ヤミヤミ ドゥ
Yami yami doo
ア、肺が もう苦しいわ
Ah, my lungs are already in pain
右に 右に
To the right, to the right,
こっち向いてよ ハニジュ
Look this way, Honey-ju
ワン
One
痛いことは 嫌いですが
I hate things that hurt, but...
君の手のひらは 嫌いじゃない
I don't hate the palm of your hand
言葉は飴玉みたいに 甘く広がって 心満たす
Words spread sweetly like candy, filling my heart
全然分かってない 永遠に言う通り
You don't get it at all, just like I always say
完全に塞がらない どこにいても
It won't completely close, no matter where I am
あー何で聴いてない 元々あの子みたいに
可愛くならなくちゃ
Ah, why aren't you listening? I have to
become cute like that girl
愛を表明しろ どこを食め
Express your love, where should I bite?
もっと愛でたいの 嫌だって分からなくなる
I want to love more, I'm losing track of what I hate
延々待った旅 手に御褒美
もう嫌だなんて 離れないように
The journey of waiting, a reward in hand
So I won't say I hate it anymore, don't leave me
今日だってちゃんと 内緒の毛繕い
Today too, I'm secretly grooming myself
にゃんたよう恋するから 愛して
Because I'm in love like a cat, love me
Everybody today is a loving day
Get it, get it, this is my courtship
Any, any, anytime, was fun with me
Give me, give me love me, my darling
愛だの間違いなんて みんなは言う
Everyone says things like love is a mistake,
取り憑かれてるって
that I'm possessed
ならこの胸で美しく 締め付けるような切なさならば
Then, if it's this beautiful, tightening pain in my chest...
選ぶ言葉と惑う指先 直せない横顔
The words I choose, my hesitant fingertips, that profile I can't fix
私しか知らない
Only I know
愛あらば無表情 もしかして
今日は優しく撫でてくれるのかな
Expressionless if there's love, perhaps
you'll stroke me gently today?
君のそれが堪えられるの 生涯で私だけなんだよね
I'm the only one in my life who can endure that of yours
あからさまに 体まさに もう嫌だって 離れられないよね
Obviously, my body is... already saying I hate it,
but we can't be apart, right?
そうだよね 感情は徐々に 舞台は徐々に
That's right, emotions gradually, the stage gradually
網羅いたしたいのよ
I want to encompass it all
...られないだけらしい
...is just how it seems.
柑橘の匂いだって
Even the citrus scent
凌ぐのだもう
I'll endure it now
この手叱られるだけらしい
This hand will just be scolded
今日だってちゃんとお膝でおとなしく
Today as well, I'll be quiet on your lap
にゃーってお好きなように
Meowing just as you like
風通して
Letting the air through
「はい喜んで」
"Yes, with pleasure"
「あなた方のため」
"For your sake"
「はい謹んで」
"Yes, with humility"
「あなた方のため」
"For your sake"
差し伸びてきた手
The hand that reached out
さながら正義仕立て
As if tailored with justice
嫌々で生き延びて
Surviving with reluctance
わからずやに盾
A shield against the stubborn
「はい喜んで あなた方のために」
"Yes, with pleasure, for your sake"
「出来ることなら 出来るとこまで」
"If I can do it, as far as I can"
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
奈落音頭奏でろ
Play the Abyss Ondo
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take another step
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Dance!)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Ring it out more!)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Dance!)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Ring it out more!)
慣らせ君の病の街を
Get used to your town of sickness
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン
Hide the laughable opinions of others
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを
Toss aside the superhumans of justice
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares
怒り抱いても
Even if you hold onto anger
優しさが勝つあなたの
Your kindness will win
欠けたとこが希望
Where you're lacking is hope
Save this game, Mr. A
救われたのは僕のうちの1人で
The one who was saved was one of us
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
奈落音頭奏でろ
Play the Abyss Ondo
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take another step
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the bad things
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares
分かれ道思うがまま Go To Earth
The fork in the road as you please, Go To Earth
任せときわがままな言葉さ
Leave it to the selfish words
奏でろハクナマタタの音は
Play the sound of Hakuna Matata
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Dance!)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Ring it out more!)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Dance!)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri Giri Dance, Giri Giri Dance (Ring it out more!)
慣らせ君の病の街を
Get used to your town of sickness
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン
Hide the laughable opinions of others
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを
Toss aside the superhumans of justice
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares
「はい喜んで」 「あなた方のため」
"Yes, with pleasure" "For your sake"
「出来ることなら 出来るとこまで」
"If I can, as far as I can"
「はい謹んで」 「あなた方のため」
"Yes, with humility" "For your sake"
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Ring out your 3 to 6 squares
アレポッチママ！
Arepocchi mama!
読者の皆様、こんにちは、お疲れ様です。すいだぽっちです！
Hello to all my readers! Good job today. I'm Suidapocchi!
ママが教えてもらった言葉で、お嬢様言葉で自己紹介します。
I'll introduce myself in lady-like language, using the words my mama taught me.
皆様ごきげんよう。
Good day, everyone.
私パヴォリア・レイネ……あ、すみません。
I am Pavolia Reine... ah, sorry.
ごきげんよう。私ホロライブインドネシア2期生パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの、以後お見知りおきを。
Good day. I am Pavolia Reine from Hololive Indonesia 2nd gen. Pleased to make your acquaintance.
本当にお嬢様でございますね。
You truly are a lady.
お嬢様ですね、完全に。
A lady, completely.
お嬢様配信！
Lady stream!
お嬢様ムービング！
Lady moving!
イエス、お嬢様ムービング！
Yes, lady moving!
レイネちゃん。
Reine-chan.
Selamat ulang tahun. Happy Birthday! おめでとう！
Selamat ulang tahun. Happy Birthday! Congratulations!
サンキ！さっきはバリガールを一緒に歌いました！
Thanks! We just sang "Bari-Girl" together!
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
どうだった？踊れてた？
How was it? Was I able to dance?
ナイス！
Nice!
もう腰が……
My lower back is already...
ノー！
No!
マッサージ、マッサージ。肩、肩お願いします肩。
Massage, massage. Shoulders, shoulders please.
ありがとうございます。これこれこれ。
Thank you. This is it, this is it.
私もマッサージが欲しい。
I want a massage too.
はい。お客様凝ってますね。
Yes. Customer, you're stiff.
ここですか？こちらですか？
Is it here? Is it there?
パーフェクトでございます。
It is perfect.
パーフェクト！
Perfect!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
Pochi-mama and Reine!
Nobody Girl!
イェーイ！
Yay!
お嬢様ハイテンションで 今日も素晴らしいです
Ojosama, today too you're wonderful
with your high tension.
さすがです
As expected.
Hari ini, today... apa ya? Gimana ngomongnya?
Today, today... what is it? How should I say it?
Did you guys see last time Pochi-mama's 3D Ohirome?
Did you guys see Pochi-mama's 3D debut last time?
そう 2人で私の3Dお披露目で
Yes, we sang and danced together...
レイネちゃんと一緒に歌って踊りました
...at my 3D debut.
And because of that, today I invited Pochi-mama
to dance and sing on stage with me!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much for inviting me!
No, thank you for coming! I had so much fun.
Jadi, apa ya? Ngomongin apa ya? What should we talk about?
So, what is it? What should we talk about?
If I remember Pochi-mama, I remember "Ojosama".
Because back then, I thought, "I'm a princess."
So I have to act like a princess, お嬢様だから
So I have to act like a princess.
日本語で、お嬢様エキティング必要必要ってね
In Japanese, "Ojosama acting" was necessary.
もう、これでパーフェクトです。さっきの動きで
That was perfect just now! With those movements.
さっきのジャンプで。OKです。こっちの動きですか？
With that jump. It was perfect. This movement?
Hololive ID お嬢様！
Hololive ID Ojosama!
皆さんもお嬢様になりたい方はね、contohしてください
If you want to be an Ojosama too,
please follow this example.
Contohって何ですか？ Contoh apa?
What is "contoh"? What example?
真似してください
Please imitate me.
そう！こんな動きがお嬢様ですよ！
Yes! This kind of movement is what Ojosama is!
本当にいいんですかね、これで
Is this really okay?
ちなみに、あのネタバレになると思うんですが
By the way, I think this is a spoiler...
今日のグッズはね、誕生日グッズはね
...but for today's goods, the birthday goods...
Pochi-mamaが頑張りました！
...Pochi-mama worked really hard on them!
描かせていただきました！皆様グッズ紹介まで
最後までしっかり見てくださいね
I was allowed to draw them! Everyone, please
watch the goods introduction until the end.
Pokoknya, katanya jangan ke mana-mana, guys
Pokoknya tunggu sampai akhir
Anyway, don't go anywhere, guys.
Please wait until the end...
Karena ada goods dari Pochi-mama sensei
...because there are goods from Pochi-mama sensei.
Kalian pasti tidak mau ketinggalan kan?
Makanya tonton sampai habis. OK?
You don't want to miss it, right?
So watch until the end. OK?
OK, kalau gitu thank you Pochi-mama for coming!
OK then, thank you Pochi-mama for coming!
この後もライブが続くので、楽しんでね！
The live will continue after this, so please enjoy!
教えて！もっとあなたの事
Tell me! More about you
(Tell me more, more, more, more)
聞かせて！もっとあなたの声
Let me hear! More of your voice
(Let me hear more, more, more)
こんなドキドキ、もう隠せない
This heartbeat, I can't hide it anymore
(Ai, I need you, Ai, I need you)
目的地はDestiny、私につけてほしいの
Destination is Destiny, I want you to join me
(もっと教えてほしい)
(I want you to tell me more)
勇気を出して
Have some courage
見つめる作戦
Staring strategy
瞳が合えば 止められない
If our eyes meet, I can't be stopped
イェイ イェイ イェイ この恋 この愛で
Yay yay yay, with this love, with this affection
メロメロ とろけちゃうよ
I'm head over heels, I'm melting
ねえ ねえ ねえ 気付いてマイダーリン
Hey hey hey, notice me, my darling
とろけちゃう 大好き
I'm melting, I love you
アイ 愛、スクリ〜ム Scream 叫びましょ
Ai, Ai, Scream, let's shout
アイ 愛、スクリ〜ム! Scream 叫びましょ
ロビちゃん！ ほーい！ なにが好き？
Lobi-chan! Yeah! What do you like?
チョコミン党！ よりは あなた！
Chocolate mint! More than that, I like you!
アユムちゃん！ はーい！ なにが好き？
Ayumu-chan! Yeah! What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバー よりは あなた！
Strawberry flavor! More than that, I like you!
シキちゃん！ はーい！ なにが好き？
Shiki-chan! Yeah! What do you like?
クッキー&クリーム よりは あなた！
Cookies & cream! More than that, I like you!
みんな！ はーい！ なにが好き？
Everyone! Yeah! What do you like?
もちろん 大好き アイスクリーム！
Of course, I love Ice Cream!
愛マスカレード
Ai Masquerade
Yeah yeah yeah
この恋心 愛で
With this heart full of love,
めろめろになっちゃうよ
I'm falling head over heels!
ねねね 気付いて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling,
とろけ大好き
I'm melting, I love you so much!
お願い見つけて My Darling
Please find me, my darling,
お願い気付いて My Darling
Please notice me, my darling!
勇気を出して
Summoning up my courage...
近付く作戦
...it's my strategy to get closer!
ぎゅっと 手が触れて
Our hands touch firmly,
止められない
and I can't stop!
Yeah yeah yeah
この恋心 愛で
With this heart full of love,
めろめろになっちゃうよ
I'm falling head over heels!
ねねね 気付いて My Darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling,
それはあなた
it's you!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
'Cause the truth is, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう
Swans, you see,
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Are kicking their feet where you can't see them
本能に忠実 忠実
Obedient and faithful to my instincts,
翻弄も十々承知
I'm fully aware of the ups and downs,
前途洋々だし
The future is bright,
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
So sometimes, I just have to take a break
Don't say "lazy"
その目でしっかり見定めて行き先
Firmly determine the destination with those eyes,
秩序お構いなしで
without worrying about the order
近道あれば それが王道
If there's a shortcut, that's the royal road,
端折れる翼あれば上等
if I have wings to skip ahead, that's top-notch!
ヤバ 爪割れた
Oh no, my nail cracked,
グルーで補修した
I fixed it with glue!
それだけで輝いた世界
With just that, the world shines
大事なのは 自分かわいがること
What's important is taking care of yourself,
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love others
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
'Cause the truth is, I'm crazy
能ある鷹はそう
Talented hawks, you see,
見えないとこにピック隠すんです
Hide their picks where you can't see them
想像に一生懸命
Working hard on imagination,
現実は絶体絶命
reality is a desperate situation
発展途上だし
I'm still developing,
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so sometimes, I suddenly go out of pitch
その目に映らないだけだってやる気は
Motivation just doesn't show in your eyes,
メーター振り切っていて
but it's actually off the charts!
いつでも全力で夢見て その分
I always dream with all my might, and in return,
全力で眠って
I sleep with all my might!
ヤバ 膝すった
Oh no, I scraped my knee,
湿布で応急した
I gave it first aid with a compress!
それだけで選んでるハイカラ
With just that, I'm choosing a stylish path
健気なのも目標 加速度つけて
Being admirable is a goal, picking up speed,
終電に臨機応変
adapting to the last train,
変幻自在勝ち
victory through being ever-changing!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
'Cause the truth is, I'm crazy
孔雀たちはそう
Peacocks, you see,
見えないとこで
where you can't see them...
…前途洋々だし…
...The future is bright, too...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
So that's why I sometimes take a break
目からやけに意思砕けちゃうんです
I'm suddenly losing my resolve
わーい！どうだった？
Yay! How was it?
How was it?
ゴンドラとかバズーカとか全部
The gondola, the bazooka, and everything...
すっごいかっこよかったでしょ？
Wasn't it very cool?
たくさん歌ったけど まだまだあるよ！
We've sung so many songs, but there's still more!
お待たせしました……
Here's the long awaited...
グッズ紹介！
Merchandise presentation!
今回も生誕グッズが出まーす！イェーイ！
We have birthday merchandise this time too! Yay!
まずはこちらですね
First is this one
青い炎の孔雀ラバーマット
Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat
Ini seperti dijanjikan ya
This is just like we promised
Just like how we said earlier, totally not spoiler
ぽちママ描き下ろし！
Illustrated by Pochi-mama!
前回のラバーマット/デスクマットを 買い逃した人が多かったので
Since many people missed out on the previous
rubber mat/desk mat,
また作っちゃいました！
We've made another one!
And for those of you who already have that rubber mat,
Well, here's... ada lagi, beda!
Well, here's... another one, but it's different!
It's different! Yay!
And along with the rubber mat,
We have the tapestry!
Ini kalian tidak tergoreng ya
You won't get burned by this
Ya apa-apalah kegoreng dikit pokoknya keren
Well, maybe just a little, but it's cool anyway
今回のライブのテーマに合わせて
Matching the theme of this live,
青い炎の孔雀タペストリー！
Peafowl of the Blue Flame Tapestry!
イラストは同じだけど 今回はタペストリー版だよ
The illustration is the same, but this time
it's a tapestry edition
こちらもぽちママ描き下ろしです！
This is also illustrated by Pochi-mama!
ぜひチェックしてね
Please check it out
続いてはこちらですね
Next is this one
Mana nih lanjutannya?
Where's the next one?
ミニマリストなデザインが好きな方へ
For those of you who like minimalist designs,
For those of you who like designs that are
more minimalistic in nature,
We have Blueming Flame Coaster.
咲き誇る青い炎のコースター！
Blueming Flame Coaster!
タペストリーやさっきのラバーマットとも デザインがぴったりだね
The design matches perfectly with the tapestry
and the rubber mat
ぽちママのイラストだよ
It's Pochi-mama's illustration
今すぐカートに入れちゃおう！
Add it to your cart right now!
あれ、まだできない？ まぁいっか！
Wait, not yet? Oh well!
そして次、さらにこちら！
And next, even more!
いつものように ボイスもあります
As always, there's also a voice pack
レイネは寿司が大好きだから
Since Reine loves sushi so much,
Because I love sushi so much, sushi daisuki...
「シークレット寿司作戦」 ボイスパックを作りました！
"Secret Sushi Strategy" voice pack!
「シークレット寿司作戦」
Secret Sushi Strategy
寿司好きなみんなもぜひ！
For all you sushi lovers too! Let's go!
最後に フルセットを購入いただいた方には
Lastly, for those who purchase the full set,
Buat yang beli full set akan ada...
For those who buy the full set, there will be...
数量限定で 直筆メッセージと 箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます
A limited number of postcards with a handwritten
message and a foil-stamped replica autograph
Limited edition postcard with a message and signature from Reine!
There's gonna be a limited edition postcard...
Buat yang beli... eh kok Indonesia lagi...
For those who buy... oops, Indonesian again...
For those people who buy the full set! Let's go!
通常版は 箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入りの ポストカードがついてきます
The standard version comes with a postcard
with a foil-stamped replica autograph and message
Yang beli biasa juga akan ada postcard yang ada message dan sign ya
Even for the regular set, there's a postcard
with a message and sign
OK!
次に 新曲を紹介します！
Next up, I'm gonna introduce my new song!
My new song... sis!
えーっと これは私の最初の…
Well, I don't know, this is my first...
...first time doing this genre, so I'm a little bit shy.
It's a little bit different from what I usually sing, so...
...I hope you guys can, even if...
...if it could resonate with you guys even for a little, I would be so happy.
こんなジャンルの曲をするの、初めてでした。
It's my first time performing a song in this genre.
だからね、ちょっとシャイです。
So, I'm a bit shy.
Yeah, well, basically, well, being placed in a box you don't exactly fit... it sucks, right?
And this is some sort of, you know, it's a song of self-acceptance.
And sometimes your flaws are what makes you you.
And even if you're broken, it's fine.
And no one else's opinions should change that.
とにかく、自分をありのままを愛していいよって曲です。
Anyway, it's a song about how it's okay to love yourself just as you are.
じゃ、あの、これから準備するので待っててね。
Well then, I'm going to get ready now, so please wait.
Please wait, 'cause I'm gonna prepare. I got a surprise!
Yay! Bye-bye!
Attention please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyats...
...who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing...
...using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine,
and I'm going to be here explaining briefly
what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership.
(That's mine, by the way.)
At The Royaltea,
our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights,
which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging
by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
which also means membership-exclusive streams
in which we can have various talks, play games together,
and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask?
Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is...
SAFETY IS GUARANTEED
...development training in which we aim to build a community of people who like living dangerously.
Welcome to The Royaltea
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
Hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey (Never, never, never gonna figure it out)
Hey, hey (Never gonna figure it out)
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Say things I never wanted to say
Up in arms, who can I please? You?
Livin' day by day
(Oh) Wake up, another bloody Monday
(Oh) Rinse and repeat until it's Sunday
(Oh) Hold it, so frustrating
Ya know, I can't do it no more
I'll say
No good, down to the core
Hear you, now I can't be
Beating down my door
Yeah, I'll shout, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough
To please you right
(I'll say)
Your idea, of ideal
That you're screaming in my hair
I'm just so broken, yeah
(Never, never, never gonna figure it out)
Hey, hey, hey
I'll stop me, hey
Or never figure it out
(Never, never, never gonna figure it out)
You want me to know what I just don't know
Put me in a hurry and then in a hole
Little did you know I'm just me, let it go
Lock me inside of a thing of your perfection, correction
Tearing me down
Am I what you like now?
Don't tell me what to do, what to say, what to...
...think about everything, but did you ever say...
I'll say
Good with being so bad, what was the issue?
I'll screw up again
Yeah, I'll shout, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough
To please you right
(I'll say)
Your idea, of ideal...
Hey! Hey! Hey!
(Never, never, never gonna figure it out!)
So broken and pathetic
I like it that way, get it
It's brutal to settle
It's never that simple, but
I'm so on to meet your harsh criteria
To that, I'm never gonna
I'm never gonna
Figure it out!
One, two!
Get loud, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much but not enough to please your eye
Your idea of ideal
That you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken
Hey! Hey!
I'll stop me
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'll never favor it out
(Never, never, never gonna figure it out!)
Figure it out!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
(Never gonna figure it out!)
PAVOLIA REINE ORIGINAL SONG
Figure it Out
SONG & MV COMING SOON
GUESTS + ANNOUNCEMENT!
MEET THE PEAFOWL OF THE BLUE FLAME
Pavolia Reine Birthday 2025
9/9 20:00 WIB / 22:00 JST